yellow.com.mt 2016-03-24

# Privacy Policy - Yellow, Discover Local - Malta & Gozo

Yellow Pages (Malta) Ltd is committed to protect you, which is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used, and we will make every effort to ensure that our activities keep within the spirit of this Policy. You can tour through most of our site without giving any information that personally identifies you, reveals personal information or allows us to contact you. At times we do require information to respond to your requests. This statement explains the data we collect from you and its use. Please note that by visiting and using our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. What Information are we gathering about visitors and how is it being used? Every computer connected to the Internet is provided with a domain name (e.g. google.com) and an IP Address (e.g. 143.232.18.134). When a visitor requests a page from within this site, our Servers automatically identify and log the HTTP request that is made to our Web Server. This information reveals nothing personal about you. In fact, very little information is automatically gathered and logged.

 **This information may include:**

• The IP address of the site that may have referred you to us  
• Your IP address  
• Operating system that you may be using (e.g. Windows XP)  
• Version and Make of Browser (e.g. Internet Explorer 7.0)

There is nothing special about the information described, and the practice of collecting this data has been generally standardized by virtually every Web Server on the Internet today. Yellow Pages (Malta) Ltd. has found it advantageous to observe visitor traffic in its aggregate, so that we can ensure maximum compatibility for the various Browsers and Operating Systems that visit our site.

**What other information does this site request?  
** We may also request your e-mail address, name, company, position, location, web address, services you may be interested in and your comments for the purposes of conducting a survey. We maintain a strict "No Spam" policy that means we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. In addition, Yellow Pages (Malta) Ltd. will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you wish to have specific communications with a member of the Yellow Pages (Malta) Ltd. staff, you will be required to provide specific information that will be routed to the appropriate contact within Yellow Pages (Malta) Ltd.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
